

# **GHENEA COZMIN**

Inginer de sistem software - Invibes

From Bucuresti

### **Contact details**

Email: cozmin.ghenea@gmail.com Tel: +40752203818

### About me

I am a very serious person and sometimes funny who really want to learn more and more about Web developing, for the moment I can say that I have experience in Front End developing like HTML CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs and a little Angular JS and JQuery, but I'm open to learn anything to get better. I have a little experience with the Back End but not as much as I really want to.

Projects- https://cozmin-ghenea.github.io/Curriculum\_Vitae/

# **Professional experience**

Experience by departments

IT Software: 4 years and 3 months

Graphics / Web design / DTP: 6 months

Client Service / Call Center: 1 year and 11 months

Jun 2019 - present

Inginer de sistem software - Invibes

2 years and 8 months

Bucharest | IT Software | IT / Telecom

Acquired skills and knowledge:

jQuery, JS, Debugging, developer tools, Window Server, HTML.

May 2018 - Jun 2019

Junior Developer - GFK Romania

1 year and 2 months

Bucharest | IT Software | IT / Telecom

Acquired skills and knowledge:

CSS, JS, HTML.

Oct 2017 - May 2018

ScriptWriter - GFK Romania

8 months

Bucharest | IT Software | IT / Telecom

I was creating an online questionnaire using their tools, and I needed just the minimum knowledge of

programming to do this task.

May 2017 - Jun 2017

Internship - Thecon

2 months

Galati | Graphics / Web design / DTP | Media / Internet

Acquired skills and knowledge:

PHP, MySQL

**Jul 2015 - May 2017**1 year and 11 months

Inserting, verification and validation operator data - Data Mondial

Galati | Client Service / Call Center | Call-Center / BPO

Acquired skills and knowledge:

 ${\bf Adobe\ Photoshop,\ Microsoft\ Office,\ microsoft\ word,\ microsoft\ excel}$ 

Dec 2016 - Mar 2017

Student - Active Design

4 months

Galati | Graphics / Web design / DTP | Media / Internet

I was student, after i graduated i got an degree in HTML & CSS & JavaScript/JQuery.

Acquired skills and knowledge: javascript / jquery, HTML/CSS

# **Education**

2019 - present Academia de Studii Economice din Bucuresti, Facultatea de Marketing

Marketing Online

2014 - 2017 Bachelor's degree - Facultatea de Economie si Administrarea Afacerilor Galati

Informatica Economica | Galati

2011 - 2015 Colegiul Economic Virgil Madgearu

Administrativ

## **Skills**

#### **General skills**

php - beginner, javascript - medium level, Bootstrap, perseverence, stress rezistance, Ambition, HTML-advanced, css - advanced, jQuery, seo optimization, good comunication

# Foreign languages

english - Intermediate

## Other info

#### Certifications

Html&CSS&JavaScript/JQuery

acquired on Dec 2016

#### **Hobbies**

Movies, swimming, Jogging

### **Driving license**

Category: B / attained: 28 Nov 2014